[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What connects muscles to bones?", "correct_answer": "Tendons", "incorrect_answers": ["Nothing", "Cartilage", "Ligaments"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who wrote the music for the movie High Noon?", "correct_answer": "Dimitri Tiomkin", "incorrect_answers": ["Walter Dormand", "Alexander Bernstein", "Dave Grusin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year did Capt. John Alcock and Lt. A.W. Brown make the first nonstop transatlantic flight?", "correct_answer": "1919", "incorrect_answers": ["1929", "1939", "1909"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Mean Girls, what present from her parents did Gretchen have to reject because Regina told her that she wasnt allowed to wear it?", "correct_answer": "Gold hoop earrings", "incorrect_answers": ["black fedora hat", "silver Fendi purse", "red Ugg boots"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The special Fanta flavour in Romania, based on a traditional local drink made from elderflower, is called by what name?", "correct_answer": "Fanta Shokata", "incorrect_answers": ["Fanta Roma", "Fanta Amanta", "Fanta Eldera"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor portrayed young Vito Corleone in the 1974 movie masterpiece The Godfather Part II?", "correct_answer": "Robert De Niro", "incorrect_answers": ["Marlon Brando", "Dustin Hoffman", "Al Pacino"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What legendary singer and actor starred in the 1962 Cold War movie The Manchurian Candidate?", "correct_answer": "Frank Sinatra", "incorrect_answers": ["Gene Kelly", "Elvis Presley", "Fred Astaire"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Did Dom DeLuise have a role in the movie Blazing Saddles?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Zoophobia is the fear of animals.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which mathematician proved that every angle can be trisected?", "correct_answer": "No one ever could", "incorrect_answers": ["Aristarcus", "Euclid", "Gauss"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What term means fear of darkness?", "correct_answer": "Achluophobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Acarophobia", "Ablutophobia", "Acerophobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the first interplanetary probe to study Venus?", "correct_answer": "Mariner 2", "incorrect_answers": ["Mariner 1", "Verona 1", "Verona 2"]}]